vapingdaily.com 2019-07-15

# Privacy Policy - Vaping Daily

Welcome to Vapingdaily.com (the “Site”) (“Us”, “We”, or VapingDaily). This Vaping Daily Privacy Policy (“Policy”) details what kind of information we collect when you use our site and its related functions, as well as how we save, store, and reveal that information to you. This Policy may be added to other notices on our site. Other Services offered by our site may also have additional privacy statements attached to them. Any personal data shared with us via the use of one of our Services constitutes an expression of consent to the movement of data to servers in the US, where they are stored, used, and disclosed in accordance with this policy.

## Information We Collect

**ON BEHALF OF THIRD PARTIES**

### YOUR PERSONAL DATA

No personal data is collected. In other words, we do not obtain your name, address, telephone number or invasive information.  
Vaping Daily does not collect any of that information at all, whether personal or invasive information.

### WHY YOUR DATA IS USED

Vaping Daily has Google Analytics, (a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, which we will refer to in the future simply as Google), connected to the website that helps us track a user’s activity. Activity such as what pages were visited before landing on our page, what links were clicked to lead to other websites, scrolling of our pages and any keystrokes in forms on our pages. No personal information is collected or stored by Google.

The reason this information is useful is to get a clearer understanding of who reads our site. Google takes all of that data and gives us a concise report of how people use the site and any demographic information which may help us improve our website.  
This means we can craft our content to better serve our readers by understanding what it is they may want by using our site.

### WHAT HAPPENS WITH THE DATA

Though we don’t collect the data ourselves, any partners or affiliates may track cookies (user data which is carried from our site to another) to be able to analyze trends or to gather information about our user base so they can effectively market their products to our site visitors. This is how specific ads can be tailored to a user’s search and explains how it seems particular ads are following them.  
You may opt out of the collection and storage of data by Google Analytics at any time. For more details on how to deactivate Google Analytics, please refer to https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.

### ON OUR BEHALF

We don’t collect or store any user data from our visitors. Cookies are enabled on our site when consented to, so we can remember users’ settings, track how the user engages with our website and understand more about the demographics of our users.  
Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

### DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION?

Vaping Daily does not collect any personal information and will not share any of that type of information with third parties.  
By posting comments on our blog pages, a user can decide for themselves how much of their personal information is seen by others reading the site. The information that might be shared with third parties only pertains to data such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc., with interested third parties to help them understand our audience activity.  
The only time Vaping Daily will share any personally identifiable information is when we may be required by law to do so. Though it is highly unlikely to occur due to the nature of our site, we may be subpoenaed and need to comply with law enforcement to provide user data. In other circumstances, it may be required on our part to share user information to protect our security or integrity of our website. This could happen if a user is trying to compromise our site, for example.

### COMPROMISE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

If personal information is compromised as a breach of security, Vaping Daily will promptly notify our customers in compliance with applicable law.

### HOW LONG IS USER INFORMATION KEPT?

If you have an e-mail subscription, we will retain your information for as long as you are subscribed. We will maintain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. To opt out of this arrangement, just unsubscribe from our email list at any time.  
If you are a visitor to the Vaping Daily, we will retain your information for as long as necessary but no longer than ten (10) years after your last visit to our sites.

### WHAT WE WOULD LIKE TO DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION

With whatever personal information you consent for us to use, we would like to be able to inform you of any news or changes related to our site, send offers or promotions or other similar instances. None of that information used for those purposes will be shared with any other parties.  
You may opt-out at any time by sending us an e-mail at info@vapingdaily.com.

### WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS?

All changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. When we materially change the policy, we will let you know via email and a prominent notice on our site, before the change becoming effective and update the ‘effective date’ at the top of this page.  
If at any point you would like to see how your information is being handled, or to opt out of any collecting of your data you have previously consented to, you can contact us at any time and let us know about your concerns.

### HOW WE COMPLY WITH THE NEW DATA PROTECTION ACT AKA GDPR

Vaping Daily takes the responsibility of safely handling our user data seriously and has taken on the additional work of complying EU GDPR framework as set forth by the European Union regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries.  
VapingDaily has certified that it adheres to the requirements of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. In other words, we will always alert our users of any breach of data, if data has been shared with another party in the case of a transfer of ownership of the website, or in the case of a law enforcement action.  
Users can ask us for access to what type of data and how it is stored by sending us an e-mail to the address provided.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy or would like more information from us, please contact us at info@vapingdaily.com.

**US Office:**  
Quit Smoking Community LLC  
1325 Drury Lane, South Lyon, MI 48178  
Phone: (650) 560-4503
